welcome back everyone
today with the help of gigachad
we are going to make an eye of Harmony
Eye of harmony is one quite complex and expensive endgame multi block
which is required for making UXV parts and progress further
the first thing we are going to do with it is condensed raw stellar plasma mixture
which is used for making magnetohydrodynamical constrained star matter
which is used in every UXV item
however making such machine is no easy task
here you can see just a few of the crafting step of just a few of its structure
and we also had to expand our crypto farm
and the power capacity of our research station
for researching such machinery
but this was still not enough
we had to tweak almost every part of our base to handle such task
and we moved to wireless energy almost everywhere
we upgraded multiple times our circuitry setups
we had to find and work around different kinds of bottlenecks
and we reached really high circuit production speeds
we built some more space elevators
for all the required materials and space processing required
we did some tinkering with our new computers
to lose less Dyson modules
and made a few more Dyson spheres
we unlocked the glowing fusion reactors
and also added some glitter to the mega blast furnaces
and we must not forget about our nanites production
let's have more nano forges
anyways now that the preparations are ready
it's time to start working on that beast
as you can see
its structure requires a lot of slow assembly line recipes
and thus we have started making more assembly lines
and we finally have completed it
this may not look that big when compared to other multi blocks
but if we get close and go inside it
we can realize it contains a pocket of space time large enough to fit a planet
however fear not
this multi-block is compliant with Time Lords' regulations and certifications
the thing we should be worrying about is the astounding amount of stuff it can output
and since this one has been overclocked too much
we now have two issues
as you can see we have a lot of buffered resources
too many resources
and the reason why these are not being taken is because we clogged our AE2 system
normal disks can only contain up to 140 million items
and the output bus seems to not like outputting into quantum chests
and thus we had to start using digital singularity cells
and so we are stocking up items
the second issue is the power eating
we have been forced into turning on out backup generator
and even though the first time the issue was just the excessive overclock amount
we still wanted to make sure we could safely afford a second eye of harmony
so we made a few more Dyson Spheres
and here we have the second eye
this time the structure has been built to support tier 4 planets
so that we can produce black dwarf matter
this time we also had to do some more tinkering with the fluids
the next tiers of eye of harmony are going to take a lot of time
so let's use this time to do some cleaning of our base
and in that time
we have managed to build a 7th tier of eye
which now contains one whole solar system
and it can produce molten universium
which is one of the components of UXV parts
the other component is the magneto hydrodynamical constrained star matter parts
which are made in an implosion compressor with weird things like an hologram projector
but before that
let's unlock the last tier of eye of harmony
the research is going super fast
thanks both to the video speed up and our new Accelerated Processing units
and after one more fix
we have finally managed to serialize the block for the most powerful version of eye of harmony
it might looks like this crafting is going super fast
and that's because we have done a lot of overclocks
other than the 16x bonus of the parallelization
however, we run out of universium for completing the project
and making more takes either a lot of time
or a lot of energy
so the way to make that recipe feasible is to reduce the overclocking settings
and replace the time dilatation fields generators
that will decrease the time taken by magnitudes at the cost of success chance
and thus we are capable of producing some universium
however we only succeed once every four times
so we are going to make some stabilization field generators
these will increase the odds and the energy output at the cost of yield
and it was then that we run into an old issue
our ae2 system is clogged again
so we made even more singularity storage cells
these are the only way to manage an eye of harmony
and thanks to the new field generators
we have finally managed to make a power positive eye of harmony
which also produces resources
now that we have universium
we can finally craft the last tier of field generators - Gallifreyan
so that we can finally harness the deep dark
and this is the result
we now have 10 planets spinning inside
and with 8 overclocks
it takes 90 seconds and 61 teraEU per tick
to make an average of 13,000 molten universium
or 2 petaEU for instant
next we made a 2700 million CPU to craft the Gallifreyan stabilization fields
meanwhile we run out of space and energy again
but fear not that was for a good cause
since we managed to finally make one eye of harmony which makes power and also resources at the same time
we get our cake and to eat it too
next we swiftly craft each UXV part to have access to every part that can currently be crafted
now that we have unlocked everything
it is time to finally start working on the final destination
for the quest, we need just one plate
but we are going to need way more
and just by looking at the recipe
we start to realize that we might need to do some more preparations
still let's start working on it just to see how it goes
the first thing is going to be the research
and since this will take some time
let's see how ae2 handles the materials for the actual crafting
it looks like we have everything required for the task
however with the current state of our factory that would take way too long
so instead of slowly building one piece
we shall not do that, and focus on first improving our base
we have not enough machines
and they are too much mixed around and on various tiers
we want to have them all sorted out and at the max tier
so let's do some tidying
and now we can do our first test run
and once all the parts are ready
we can start the dedicated advanced assembly line
we are going to use the first plate we made to research the next part we are going to need
and after a lot of time
we have the next recipe unlocked
however our base is still not ready
since we drained all of our energy just for this test run
so we added a bunch more of them
and now we have a positive energy production
all we have to do now is make circuits in bulks of 1 million
then we do a bunch more of craftings with ae2
we do some occasional debugging and plumbing
such as the dtpf getting stuck due to reaching the limit of catalyst accumulated by the discounts
and once everything is working nicely and fine
after some AFK time
we can manually craft the Stargate base
we do that manually to increase the value of the block
who wants an artifact such as that to be made in an industrial way
I'm not going to show you all the crazy work that ae2 did
but that's the leftovers
and after about 4 months of AFK
we have finally managed to get the last part
now we can finally claim the reward for the highest task one can do in this pack
4 iron ingots and 3 sticks
the only task left to do is to find out how to assemble it
since there isn't much documentation on it
and after many trials, we managed to make it work finally
and it turns out that with only one Stargate we are going nowhere
time to get back to work
欢迎回来，各位
今天在gigachad的帮助下
我们要做鸿蒙之眼
鸿蒙之眼是一个相当复杂和昂贵的大后期多方块
而它是制造UXV部件和进一步发展所必需的
我们要做的第一件东西是浓缩原始恒星等离子体混合物
用于制造磁流体约束恒星物质
它将用于每个UXV物品的制造
然而制造这样的机器并非易事
你欣赏一下它的几个结构方块的制作步骤
我们还必须升级算力
以及研究站的发电能力
才能研究这种机器
但这还不够
我们不得不调整基地几乎
每一个部分来处理这样的任务
我们几乎给所有机器用上了无线能源
我们多次升级电路板自动化
我们发现各种瓶颈问题，解决它们
我们达到了很高的电路生产速度
我们又造了一些太空电梯
用于所有所需的材料和太空处理
我们对新电脑做了些修补
以损失更少的戴森模块
并多做了几个戴森球
我们解锁了发光的聚变反应堆
并在巨高炉中添加了一些闪光
纳米蜂群的生产也不能忘
让我们造更多的纳米锻炉
不管怎样，现在准备工作已经好了
是时候开始对付那只野兽了
如你所见
它的结构需要很多缓慢的装配线配方
因此我们开始制造更多的装配线
我们终于完成了它
与其他多方块相比，这可能看起来没那么大
但如果我们飞进去
我们意识到它能装下一整颗行星
但不要害怕
此多方块符合时间领主的规定和认证
我们应该担心的是
它输出的惊人数量的东西
由于它超频了太多
我们现在有两个问题
如你所见，它缓存了很多东西
过于多的东西
这些东西没有进AE的原因是
AE系统已经爆满
普通磁盘最多只能装下1.40亿个东西
输出总线似乎不喜欢输出到量子箱
因此，我们必须开始使用数字奇点单元
这样我们就能存下很多东西了
第二个问题是电力消耗
我们被迫打开备用发电机
尽管第一次的问题只是超频量过大
我们仍然想确保我们能安全地
负担起第二只鸿蒙之眼的消耗
所以我们又做了几个戴森球
这就是第二个EoH
这次建造的结构能容纳四级行星
这样我们才能产生黑矮星物质
这一次，我们还必须对液体进行更多的处理
鸿蒙之眼的下一级要花很多时间
所以让我们利用这段时间来清理基地
在这段时间里
我们成功建造了第7级的EoH
现在它包含了一个完整的太阳系
它可以产生熔融宇宙素
这是UXV零件的一部分
另一部分是磁流体约束恒星物质
它们是在聚爆压缩机中放入
类似全息投影仪这种奇怪的东西制造的
但在那之前
让我们解锁最后一级的鸿蒙之眼
研究进展得非常快
这得感谢剪辑加速和新的APU
再经过一次修复后
我们终于成功并行制造了
满级鸿蒙之眼的结构方块
这个合成看起来似乎非常快
那是因为除了并行的16倍加成
我们还做了很多超频
然而，我们用完了这个项目所需的宇宙素
制造更多的宇宙素需要很多时间
或者很多能量
因此，使该配方可行的方法是减少超频设置
并更换时间膨胀场发生器
这将以成功概率为代价减少大量时间
这样，我们就有能力生产宇宙素
然而我们的配方每四次才成功一次
所以我们要做一些稳定场发生器
这些将增加配方成功几率
和能量输出，但代价是产量降低
就在这时，我们遇到了老问题
我们的AE系统又堵塞了
所以我们制造了更多的奇点存储单元
这些是管理鸿蒙之眼输出的唯一方法
多亏了新的稳定场发生器
我们总算成功创造了一个能发电的鸿蒙之眼
它也产生了很多资源
现在我们有宇宙素了
我们终于可以制造最后一级的场发生器了
这样我们就能收获深暗世界的资源
这就是做出来的样子
我们现在有10颗行星在里面旋转
并带有8次超频
它将花费90秒和61万亿EU/t
平均制造1.3万L的熔融宇宙素
或者一口气用 2e15 EU
接下来，我们制作一个27亿容量
的CPU来制作鸿蒙稳定场
与此同时，我们又耗尽了主网空间和电量
别慌，这可是个好兆头
因为这个EoH同时产出电量与资源
我们真正地“自食其果”
接下来，我们快速制作当前可获得的所有UXV部件
既然我们已经解锁了一切
是时候开始研究最终目的地了
为了任务，我们只需要一个盘子
但我们还会需要更多
只要看看配方
此时便可以意识到需要更多的准备
还是让我们开始研究它，看看进展如何
第一件事是研究
因为这需要一些时间
让我们看看AE如何处理实际制作的材料
看起来任务所需的东西我们都有了
然而，以我们工厂的现状，这需要太长时间
所以与其慢慢地磨出一套来
我们更倾向于升级基建
我们机器太少
它们各种电压都有
让我们将其整理出来，全部换成最高电压
所以让我们整理一下
现在我们可以进行第一次试运行了
一旦所有部件都准备好了
我们可以启动专用的进阶装配线
我们将使用我们制作的第一个盘子
来研究我们需要的下一个零件
经过很长时间
我们解锁了下一个配方
然而我们的基地还没有准备好
因为我们为了这次测试耗尽了所有的电量
所以我们又加了一堆
现在我们有一个正的能量产出
我们现在只需要以100万为单位下单电路板
然后借助AE再多做一些合成工作
我们偶尔做一些调试和疏通管道
如dtpf因达到折扣累积的催化剂极限而卡住
一旦一切正常
挂机一段时间后
我们可以手动合成星门基座
手搓这个方块以增加它的价值
谁会希望这样的神器以工业化的方式制造出来
我不会向你展示AE所做的所有疯狂工作
但那是剩下的东西了
挂机4个月后
我们终于设法完成了最后一部分
现在我们终于可以领取
这个整合包终极任务的奖励了
4个铁锭和3根棍子
剩下的唯一任务就是找出如何组装它
因为没有多少操作说明
经过多次试验我们终于成功了
结果发现只有一个星门我们无处可去
该回去工作了
（上期the cake is a lie的callback）